How you doing there?
>> Pretty good. How you doing?
>> Good. Just when when you sat down,
started looking at at your options, what
was it about, you know, this team, uh,
this offense that that just kind of
seemed to fit.
>> Um, it's it's explosive. Everything, all
the weapons, everything in this offense
and this game, it's built for explosion.
Um, and then also being able to be back
home with the fam is is another just key
component.
>> Your family do you still have here,
Larry?
>> Uh, a lot. My whole family's still here.
So, I'm the I grew up in Oak Park, was
born in Detroit. Um, went to Brother
Ice, went to Oak Park schooling growing
up until high school. Um, I'm a hometown
kid, so all my family still here.
>> How excited is the family that that
you're coming home?
>> Extremely ecstatic. My mom is she was
crying as soon as I called her and told
her.
>> Keep track of Detroit when you were Have
you always been a Lions fan? And when
you were in Chicago, M how much were you
always keeping track?
>> Yeah. You know, it's funny cuz I feel
like a lot of players, no matter who you
play for, you always have like a I'm
going to go check and see how my team is
doing. You know what I mean? So, I
always check and look and yeah, I've
I've been a fan.
>> How do you see yourself fitting into,
you know, this this this team and
helping this squad with your skill set?
>> Uh, just being big, physical, and being
able to move. I feel like that's key
components is being a good offensive
lineman. And I feel like I can do all
three of those things and can do them
well.
>> What was the moment like when you put
the uh pen to paper to come back home?
>> It's surreal. It it it still doesn't
feel real cuz like this is this is home.
So it's I don't really know how to
explain it to people, but it it doesn't
it's I'm a sad guy. I can't really put
words to it.
>> Is there anything in particular outside
of the family that you're looking
forward to to being around? Uh
>> no, really just the fam. I mean, I kind
of know everything else like in the area
and whatnot. So really just being with
the fam and being able to be with them
year round instead of just, you know,
like offseason or going back and forth
between OTAAS.
>> Explain a little bit more just about or
tell us a little bit more about the the
phone call with your mom. When was it
when you decided, you know, to come?
>> Uh, as soon as I called the phone, my
agent, I called her and she was almost
breaking down. Um, she she's my rock.
She's everything. Um, her and my wife's
over there. I don't want to get
emotional up here, but yeah, she's she
means the world. You knew obviously this
was a possibility before you know Monday
or whatever. So had you told her this
might be a possibility? What?
>> No, I didn't. I honestly didn't know. Um
I mean whenever my agent called me once
that period started um was it Monday
when temper started? I mean we weighed
out our options and and told her almost
a no-brainer. So
beyond the um you know the financial
component of free agency uh what was
maybe the team's pitch to you or your
agent about you know coming to Detroit?
Um, honestly, it wasn't a super big like
just pitch from them. I mean, we just
weighed our options and seeing what the
best best fit would be and just went
with that.
>> You were a 11 game starter last year.
You know, do you um do you expect to
start for this team?
>> Um, you know, I played four different
positions over my career. So, in any way
I can help the team and just help us
move forward, you know, I'm willing to
do whatever whether I start and not
start and not really just a I'm a team
player.
>> What about um right tackle versus left
tackle? I mean, a lot of people are sort
of penciling you in for the right tackle
spot, moving pane to left. What What
have they told you about that?
>> Uh, honestly, not too much. You have to
talk to talk to the headman.
>> You did mention you've played all four
spots. We hear that a lot with guys that
they'll, you know, play wherever the the
team needs you. Do you have a favorite?
Um, honestly,
no. I mean, honestly, no. No, I don't.
>> It's just more about knowing you're
going to be in one spot. Is that
>> I think that's the biggest thing. I
mean, kind of having a a fluid
understanding of just one position, you
know what I mean? But, I mean, I've been
the swing. I've been I've been some of
everything. So, I don't think a playbook
or anything is the issue. It's just more
so just working out at one spot.
>> Have you had a chance to talk to to
Frank yet? and just maybe what those
conversations initially went like, how
much you're looking forward to working
with him, and then maybe just also
opposite a guy like Penet, you know, one
of the best in in in the business at the
position.
>> Yeah. Um, haven't really talked too
much, uh, Hank. Um, I'll talk to him
shortly, but um, I've known Paneet since
we got the same agent. I've known him
pre-draft. Um, been been a close friend
of mine, so it's it's fun to get back to
work with him. What was your impression
of Dan Campbell from afar and have you
had any interactions with him yet?
>> Man, he's he's a fiery guy. Uh he gets
after it. Um he cares about his players
like a lot. Like you can you can being
from another team and just watching
them, you can tell how much he truly
cares about everyone in this building.
So it's an honor. It's an honor.
>> This is the first year like free agents
have been allowed to have video, you
know, meetings with teams like in that
once that period opens. Did you have
those with teams and and what impact or
what benefit do you think there was to
that? Uh, no, I didn't. Personally, I
didn't have any. Um, I think there's
there's a good benefit from that. I
mean, just being able to talk to maybe
it's a I don't know the specific rules
or maybe it's a position coach calling
somebody or you know what I mean? So, I
mean, that could be that could be good.
You
>> talk about your connection to to
Detroit, just Detroiters carry Detroit
close to their heart. Just how much did
this city
>> help you become the person you are now?
And just how much you look at just car
having that jersey on, man, just repping
the deal.
>> Yeah, it it it grew me into the man I am
today. You know, this city is is nothing
but people that get up and get after it.
You know what I'm saying? Like, it's
nothing but hustlers. People people are
hard workers in this city. And I take
that with a lot of pride. So, being from
from here and being able to put the
jersey on is is everything cuz I know
it's representing everybody that's they
ain't want to get up today. Everybody,
you know what I mean? So, everybody that
gets up and and want and have to get
after it is what it represents.
>> You made your uh first big move in the
NFL. you four years in Chicago, then you
moved to Miami, and now you're here.
What about going to Miami last year can
help you maybe acclimate quickly uh at
your new stop here?
>> Um,
going to Miami, I think it reinstilled a
lot of confidence in me and just being
very, very overly confident with my play
style and the way I have success in this
league. So, being able to bring that
from there to here is everything.
>> What other teams I guess were you
looking at here this this week? Was
Chicago an option possibly?
>> No, Chicago was not an option. Uh
there's a couple other teams.
Just keep it at that.
>> You still did you still keep your
offseason home here or have you been
living?
>> Yeah. No, I'm here. I'm here offseason.
Yep.
>> Little drive over then, huh?
>> Yeah, that's it.
>> You close with any other guys on the
team?
>> Um Andis went to Missou. Um as I was
coming out, he was coming in. Um
Pane, that's about it. about it.
>> This opportunity for you, you're part of
a changing of the guard of the sense on
this line. Do you look at that as an
opportunity to kind of set your own
definition here or does that come with a
lot of pressure?
>> Can you repeat that? I'm sorry.
>> Sure. Just your entry into this is part
of a bit of a changing of the guard on
the line. So, do you look at that as a
positive opportunity or do you think
that comes with a little pressure?
>> No, I think it's positive. I think um I
think it's very positive. um I get to
kind of set my own
standards or you know what I mean how
people look at you. So I think it's it's
very positive.
>> And in your relationship with P that
you've kept up, what has he told you
kind of about the culture set?
>> Um it's I mean the culture is the
culture is awesome. So it's he's
explained it u we talked about it. It
was good.
>> You guys beat Kaid yet? And and what do
you think you guys you know can
collectively help this offensive line
do?
>> Um just bring a physical style to play.
It's already very physical. Um, just
keep the standard. The standard, you
know what I mean?